[
        {"question":"5+5", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"0", "ans3":"10","ans4":"11","correct":"10","number":"1"},
        {"question":"5-5", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"0", "ans3":"10","ans4":"11","correct":"0","number":"2"},
        {"question":"5*5", "ans1":"25", "ans2":"5", "ans3":"10","ans4":"15","correct":"25","number":"3"},
        {"question":"5/5", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"1", "ans3":"10","ans4":"15","correct":"1","number":"4"},
        {"question":"10+10", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"0", "ans3":"10","ans4":"20","correct":"20","number":"5"},
        {"question":"5+5+10", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"20", "ans3":"10","ans4":"11","correct":"20","number":"6"},
        {"question":"5-5+10", "ans1":"5", "ans2":"0", "ans3":"10","ans4":"11","correct":"10","number":"7"},
        {"question":"5+5*10", "ans1":"55", "ans2":"100", "ans3":"10","ans4":"5","correct":"55","number":"8"},
        {"question":"5*5+10", "ans1":"55", "ans2":"35", "ans3":"10","ans4":"5","correct":"35","number":"9"},
        {"question":"5/5+10", "ans1":"1", "ans2":"0", "ans3":"10","ans4":"11","correct":"11","number":"10"}
    ]
